# **Gregoire Glachant**

e-mail: greg.gla@gmail.com +66832677741

## Summary

Over 20 years' experience creating digital content. Started working in video games in my teens before exploring video and print. Driven by connecting people with brands through great stories and now leveraging past experience and skills to deliver omni-channel content marketing solutions to clients, from beer makers Singha to commercial bank Kiatnakin Phatra Financial Group.

# **Employment**

Asia City Media Group Thailand)

Bangkok, Thailand

2006 - present

Editor in Chief, Product Director

August 2015-present

- Doubled BK Magazine's reach, which now stands at 500,000 people per week on Facebook and 400,000 unique visitors per month on bkmagazine.com.
- Built Asia City Media Group's content marketing offerings through effective native ads that consistently outperform the industry average 10:1.
- Led team of 17 people creating publications both under our own brands (BK Magazine, Where, Soimilk) and for a range of clients from banks and alcohol brands to government agencies.
- 196% growth in digital revenue from Q4 '14 to Q4 '15.

Reference: Duke Theerathada, Executive Vice-President, Corporate Brand and Communications, TMB Bank

#### Managing Editor, Product Director

February 2009 - August 2015

 Developed a print magazine into a truly multi-platform product which saw explosive growth in social media (from zero to 100,000 Facebook fans) and online traffic (from zero to 800,000 monthly page views) and mobile apps.

Reference: James Fuss, Country Manager, Asia City Media Group

#### **Deputy Editor**

July 2006 - February 2009

 Managed writers, liaised with the art director, sub-edited and wrote for BK Magazine, Bangkok's premier lifestyle weekly with 30,000 copies in print.

### Freelance Producer, Author

Paris and Bangkok

1998 - 2006

- Produced multimedia content for various platforms, including video games by American company THO.
- Produced fashion show videos for designers based in Paris, such as Kenzo and Jean-Claude Jitrois.
- Wrote for publications such as WestEast (Hong Kong), Blast (Paris) and the Phuket Gazette (Phuket).

#### Cryo Interactive / Virgin Interactive

Paris, France

1993 - 1996

 Co-author and director with Nic Mathieu of video game Hardline, a live-action FMV-based computer game released internationally in 1996.

# Education

ESEC Graduation 1998

Electronic Arts Major at École Supérieure d'Études Cinématographiques, Paris, France

# Lycée International de Saint Germain-en-Laye

**Graduation 1995** 

International Option Baccalaureate (American Section) in economics with honors

## Skills and Interests

Perfectly bilingual in French and English (French nationality, lived in the USA as a child). Limited working Thai.

Avid travel photographer and obsessed with modern architecture and vintage motorcycles.